#this is the priority section

ranking page -> supporters list 

vip -> in that the badges and there amt must be listed and along with that must be editable.
levels ->

there must be list
crown - streaming levels (by diamonds receiving)
sheild - supportig levels (coin sending)


## this is 


agency  - create agency (select subadmin, select master agency, user id )
move agency 


in the master agency tab (5%) - create master agency (choose sub-admin, email, password)

in the subadmin (5%)- create subadmin(email and password)



admin has his particular agency


remove royals from master and subadmin 
subadmin page 

5%  of agency's revenue = goes to master agency
5% of master agency = goes of subadmin